pro100usa.com 2019-03-30

# Policies

We have updated Privacy Policy and [Terms of Use](https://www.pro100usa.com/pro100-terms-of-use "Terms of use"), effective May 24, 2018. We recommend that you read this in full to ensure you are fully informed. These changes were made primarily in preparation for the EU’s new data privacy law, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). We use cookies to offer you a better browsing experience, analyze site traffic, personalize content, and serve targeted advertisements. If you continue to use this site, you consent to our use of cookies.

## Data Protection Rights

 **You may have the following data protection rights:**

To access, correct, update or request deletion of Personal Information. Pro100USA takes reasonable steps to ensure that the data we collect is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete and up to date. As a Member, you may contact us directly by [contacting us.](https://www.pro100usa.com/contact-us "Contact us") In addition, individuals who are residents of the EEA can object to processing of their Personal Information, ask to restrict processing of their Personal Information or request portability of their Personal Information. You can exercise these rights by contacting us using the contact form under ‘About Us’ section.

Similarly, if Personal Information is collected or processed on the basis of consent, the data subject can withdraw their consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your Personal Information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent. If you receive these requests in form of newsletter subscription you can decide to opt out of receiving such marketing.

The right to complain to a data protection authority about the collection and use of Personal Information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority. Contact details for data protection authorities in the EEA are available here. We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection law. We may ask you to verify your identity in order to help us respond efficiently to your request. If we receive a request, we will either reach out to you, or, if appropriate, we may respond directly to their request.

Pro100USA will not sell, trade, or transfer any personally identifiable information  to outside parties or affiliates. The information you provide, whether public or private, will not be given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. Your information is solely for the following purposes: -

To personalize your experience

To improve customer service  
Help us effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs  
To process transactions  
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature  
To send periodic emails  
To send you information and updates pertaining to your computer issues, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

#### EXCEPTION:

Distribution of Information  
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
